<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Danielle Chen</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Danielle Chen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Where will a new guest book their first Airbnb travel?</title>
      <link>/projects/2017-05-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/2017-05-04/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR In this project, we use an Airbnb new users booking dataset to predict the users’ country destination. The dataset come from a previous Kaggle competition. We tried SVM, Random forest, and Xgboost separately and an ensembled model utilizing all three models. XGBoost performed the best. The accuracy rate is 71%.
 ✈Introduction Airbnb enables people to lease or rent short-term lodging including vacation rentals, apartment rentals, homestays, hostel beds, or hotel rooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survival Analysis of Randomized Placebo-controlled Trial of HIV-1 disease</title>
      <link>/projects/2017-01-04-survival-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 17:44:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/2017-01-04-survival-analysis/</guid>
      <description>1.TL;DR In this analysis, survival Cox-ph model shows that portential risk factors for HIV-1 includes whether or not patients receive previous treatments (tx), patients’ ability to tolerate chemotherapy (karnof) and patient’s baseline cd4 counts (cd4). Exploratory analysis on mean, median survival time for HIV patients and non patients were compared before performing the model. This is the analysis I did when I took Survival Analysis course (BST 222) at UC Davis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About me I&amp;rsquo;m a product analyst working in San Francisco Bay Area. I am an innovative, creative, self-motived person. I embrace challenge, actively learn new techniques and find out opportunities to apply data analysis skills.
 2020 Jun Data Scientist, Growth at Atlassian 2019 Jul - 2020 Apr Product Analyst, Growth at Thumbtack (Professional marketplace company).  Pro Growth Team - I provided analytical support in professional onboarding experience (Ex: projects related to getting pros early committement, converting web users to app users) and partnered with PMs, engineers and designers to optimize products to better serve new pros.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>